<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="locale">en</string>
	<string name="which_software">Which forum software are you using?</string>
	<string name="multiple_files">The importer found multiple import data files. Please choose the one you wish to use.</string>
	<string name="not_here">It's not here!</string>
	<string name="start_conversion">Start conversion</string>
	<string name="check_more"><![CDATA[If the software you're looking for doesn't appear above, please check to see if it is available for download at <a href="https://github.com/openimporter/openimporter/">Github</a>. If it isn't, we may be able to write one for you - just ask us!]]></string>
	<string name="having_problems"><![CDATA[If you're having any other problems with this importer, don't hesitate to look for help.]]></string>
	<string name="not_found"><![CDATA[The importer did not find any import data files. Please check to see if the one you want is available for download at <a href="https://github.com/openimporter/openimporter/">Github</a>. If it isn't, we may be able to write one for you - just ask us!]]></string>
	<string name="not_found_download"><![CDATA[After you download it, simply upload it into the same folder as <b>this import.php file</b>. If you're having any other problems with this importer, don't hesitate to look for help.]]></string>
	<string name="try_again">Try again!</string>
	<string name="settings_not_found">This importer was unable to find %s in the path you specified. Please double check the path, and that it is already installed there.</string>
	<string name="open_basedir">The importer detected that your host has open_basedir enabled on this server. Please ask your host to disable this setting or try moving the contents of your %s to the public html folder of your site.</string>
	<string name="config_not_found">Unable to find the settings for %s. Please double check the path and try again.</string>
	<string name="password_incorrect">The database password you entered was incorrect. Please make sure you are using the right password and try it again. If in doubt, use the password from Settings.php.</string>
	<string name="select_step">You must select at least one step to import.</string>
	<string name="permission_denied"><![CDATA[Sorry, the database connection information used in the specified installation of your forum cannot access the installation of %2$s. This may either mean that the installation doesn't exist, or that the MySQL account used does not have permissions to access it.<br /><br />The error MySQL gave was: %1$s']]></string>
	<string name="before_continue">Before you continue</string>
	<string name="before_details"><![CDATA[This importer assumes you have already installed the destination forum and that your installation is working properly.<br />It copies members, posts and other data from your &quot;source&quot; installation of %s into the &quot;destination&quot; installation of %s.  It <strong>won't work</strong> without an installation of your destination forum.<p>All or some of the data in your installation of your destination forum will be <b>overwritten</b>.  Your source data will not be changed.</p>]]></string>
	<string name="destination_installed">Try again!</string>
	<string name="to_what">Import to which platform?</string>
	<string name="where">Where are they?</string>
	<string name="locate_destination">The importer only needs to know where the two installations are, after which it should be able to handle everything for itself.</string>
	<string name="locate_source">The importer need to know in to which software you are importing your forum.</string>
	<string name="advanced_options">Advanced options</string>
	<string name="path_to">Path to %s</string>
	<string name="path_from">Path to %s</string>
	<string name="restart_after">pause script after (seconds)</string>
	<string name="countdown">Javascript countdown (sleep)</string>
	<string name="right_path">This may be the right path.</string>
	<string name="change_path">You will need to change the value in this box.</string>
	<string name="database_passwd">database password</string>
	<string name="database_verify">The MySQL password (for verification only).</string>
	<string name="selected_only">Import selected areas only</string>
	<string name="empty_log">Empty the importer's error log?</string>
	<string name="continue">Continue</string>
	<string name="not_this">Not this software?</string>
	<string name="skipped">skipped</string>
	<string name="not_found_skipped">not found, skipped</string>
	<string name="pick_different"><![CDATA[If this is the wrong software, you can go back and <a href="%s">pick a different data file</a>.]]></string>
	<string name="recalculate">Recalculating statistics</string>
	<string name="importing">Importing</string>
	<string name="complete">Import complete!</string>
	<string name="congrats">Congratulations, the importer has completed successfully.</string>
	<string name="check_box">Please check this box to delete the importer right now for security reasons.</string>
	<string name="delete_successful">OpenImporter directory has been successfully removed from the server.</string>
	<string name="delete_not_successful">OpenImporter was not able to remove its directory from the server:  Remember to delete it manually.</string>
	<string name="may_fail">doesn't work on all servers.</string>
	<string name="not_done">Not quite done yet!</string>
	<string name="importer_paused"><![CDATA[The importer has paused a few seconds to avoid overloading your server. Don't worry though, <b>nothing's wrong</b>.]]></string>
	<string name="all_imported">Now that everything is imported, your destination forum should have all the data from the %s installation.</string>
	<string name="smooth_transition">We hope you had a smooth transition!</string>
	<string name="valid">installation valid</string>
	<string name="invalid">invalid path, installation could not be validated!</string>
	<string name="validated">installation validated!</string>
	<string name="overall_progress">Overall progress</string>
	<string name="error_message">Message: %s</string>
	<string name="error_trace">Trace: %s</string>
	<string name="error_line">Line: %s</string>
	<string name="error_file">File: %s</string>
	<string name="db_unsuccessful">Unsuccessful!</string>
	<string name="db_query_failed">This query: %s</string>
	<string name="db_error_caused">Caused the error: %s</string>
	<string name="imported_from">Forum imported from %s</string>
	<string name="to">to</string>
</resources>